<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Dehradun Handbook</string>
    <string name="places">Places</string>
    <string name="food">Food</string>
    <string name="leisure">Leisure</string>
    <string name="utility">Utility</string>
    <string name="r1_name">Prez</string>
    <string name="r1_desc">Prez offers a fine dining experience in an excellent ambience. The restaurant is elegantly done up in pinewood and has a bar also. It is located next to Hotel President in Astley Hall, Rajpur Road.</string>
    <string name="r2_name">Pavilion, Hotel President Coffee Shop</string>
    <string name="r2_desc">Located in Astley Hall, Hotel President is a landmark of Dehradun and favourite of Doonites since decades. The hotel has few but well appointed rooms. It has a bar and coffee shop. The continental food here is excellent.</string>
    <string name="r3_name">Black Pepper Bar and Restaurant</string>
    <string name="r3_desc">A fine multicuisine restaurant also in Astley Hall. It is very popular for its good quality preparations and excellent service. It has a bar also.</string>
    <string name="r4_name">My Wife\'s Place</string>
    <string name="r4_desc">Located opposite Meedo\'s Grand Hotel on Rajpur Road, it is well known for its North Indian fare, kebabs and Mughlai dishes.</string>
    <string name="r5_name">Town Table</string>
    <string name="r5_desc">Also on Rajpur Road, near Hotel Great Value. Town Table is a new entrant among Dehradun’s restaurants. The ambience is great and the menu is not run of the mill. The dessert selection is excellent.</string>
    <string name="r6_name">Kumar Foods</string>
    <string name="r6_desc">A well known joint on Rajpur Road. This multicuisine restaurant serves Chinese, Indian and Continental food.</string>
    <string name="r7_name">Moti Mahal</string>
    <string name="r7_desc">Located near the Clock Tower on Rajpur Road. Famous for North Indian food.</string>
    <string name="r8_name">Kumar Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="r8_desc">Located on Rajpur Road it is one of the oldest restaurants in town and serves only vegetarian food.</string>
    <string name="r9_name">Grille</string>
    <string name="r9_desc">Grille is a buffet restaurant in Rajpur Road\'s Axiom.</string>
    <string name="r10_name">Barbeque Nation</string>
    <string name="r10_desc">The unique DIY concept caught the fancy of food-lovers across India as Barbeque Nation offered both vegetarian and non-vegetarian menus. Barbeque Nation finally came to Dehradun and is located on Rajpur Road near Parsvnath Eleganza.</string>
    <string name="r11_name">Kalsang Restaurant</string>
    <string name="r11_desc">Kalsang Restaurant is a branch of the famous outlet in Mussoorie. They have a great selection of Tibetan cuisine and some great ambiance and views to offer.</string>
    <string name="r12_name">Punjab Grill</string>
    <string name="r12_desc">Fine dining restaurant chain famous for it\'s authentic Punjabi cuisine. Punjab Grill is the amalgam of the royal tastes and the Sikh flavors has placed Punjab on a high culinary pedestal. The food fit for the royals!</string>
    <string name="l1_name">Buffet</string>
    <string name="l1_desc">A small coffee and sandwich joint opposite Gandhi Park on Rajpur Road. Easy on the pocket, it is very popular with Doon\’s youngsters. The sandwiches, bread pakora and burgers are tasty and very reasonably priced.</string>
    <string name="l2_name">Chicken Point</string>
    <string name="l2_desc">A non vegetarian takeaway joint located opposite Vishal Mega Mart on Rajpur Road. It serves lip smacking kebabs. All tandoori items are worth trying specially the Chicken Seekh Kebab.</string>
    <string name="l3_name">Chetan Poori Wala</string>
    <string name="l3_desc">When Doonites want to have a heavy Sunday brunch or when unexpected guests come and mom is not in the mood to cook, Chetan poori wallah near Hanuman Chowk is the place to head for to get pooris packed along with Aloo and Kaddu Sabzi. A true blue Doonite has definitely had Chetan ki Pooris.</string>
    <string name="l4_name">Pakodewale Sardar Ji</string>
    <string name="l4_desc">Located in Rajpur village, Sardarji\'s is a favourite haunt of Doonites specially on Sundays. The charm lies both in the long drive up to Rajpur village and getting to eat Sardarji\’s yummy pakoras with the delicious imli chutney along with a cup of garam Chai.</string>
    <string name="l5_name">Dwarka Chowk Bun Tikki Wala</string>
    <string name="l5_desc">Doonites are very fond of Bun Tikkis. Bun Tikkis are reasonable, filling and tasty. Many localities have their own favourite Bun Tikki Walla. Another well known one is the Bun Tikki Walla at Race Course. Can beat the McAloo Tikki any day!</string>
    <string name="l6_name">Maggi Points</string>
    <string name="l6_desc">A series of small shacks dotting the road from Dehradun to Mussoorie. They serve Maggi noodles and chai. Somehow the Maggi served at these joints always tastes very delicious. Maybe, this is due to the wonderful view of Dehradun City from these joints.</string>
    <string name="l7_name">Countdown Restaurant</string>
    <string name="l7_desc">A well known Chinese joint on Subhash Road near Pacific Hotel. It serves generous portions and is reasonably priced. Before the fast food chains opened up, it was a favourite joint with Doon youngsters to give their friends a birthday treat.</string>
    <string name="l8_name">Dilli Chaat Wala</string>
    <string name="l8_desc">Located opposite NIVH on Rajpur Road just short of Jakhan, Dillii Chaat Walla serves tangy chaat having all the seasonal fresh fruits with pieces of fried potato. His claim to fame besides the delicious fruit chaat is that he was invited to put up his stall at Indian Captain Mahendra Singh Dhoni\'s wedding which took place in Dehradun.</string>
    <string name="c1_name">Cafe Coffee Day</string>
    <string name="c1_desc">Branches: Rajpur Road, Jakhan, Astley Hall, Race Course, Chakrata Road (near FRI gate)</string>
    <string name="c2_name">Barista</string>
    <string name="c2_desc">The chain has many locations in Dehradun, the main one being on Rajpur Road.</string>
    <string name="c3_name">Orchard Cafe and Restaurant</string>
    <string name="c3_desc">Orchard is tucked away in quiet lane of the Rajpur village very close to the MDDA Park near Pakodewale Sardarji. Inspite of its quiet location, which one thinks nobody knows, one invariably bumps into a familiar face while at the Orchard. The scenic view and the great music playing here have made this place very popular with Doonites. The renovated new look has added to the ambience of the place. Tibetan, Chinese and Thai dishes are served here.</string>
    <string name="c4_name">Jail Cafe</string>
    <string name="c4_desc">A mock jail where the policemen serve you coffee. Jail Cafe is located in Pacific Hills, the newest hotspot in town.</string>
    <string name="c5_name">TBistro</string>
    <string name="c5_desc">TBistro is located near Crossroads Mall. They serve excellent tea and great food to go along with it. The bistro is full with people and is a popular hangout place for the local teenagers.</string>
    <string name="c6_name">Best Buddy\'s Restro Cafe</string>
    <string name="c6_desc">Best Buddy\'s is one of those newly opened joints in town that everyone will visit for sure. Great selection of food.</string>
    <string name="c7_name">Razzmatazz Cafe</string>
    <string name="c7_desc">This newly opened, semi-outdoor cafe in Dalanwala is a worderful place to hang out with friends. The shakes are great and the whole decor and theme has a nice aesthetic appeal.</string>
    <string name="c8_name">First Gear Cafe</string>
    <string name="c8_desc">As the name suggests, the only way to get to this cafe on Mussoorie road is by using your first gear. The cafe offers great selection of food and beverages with breathtaking views of the hills.</string>
    <string name="c9_name">Y Cafe</string>
    <string name="c9_desc">Y Cafe is Hotel White House\'s modern image with great hand-beaten coffee, thin-crust pizzas and other offerings. It also has outdoor seating in a garden if you\'re feeling that vibe.</string>
    <string name="c10_name">Kalsang AMA Cafe</string>
    <string name="c10_desc">This is the same AMA Cafe from Delhi. Below Kalsang Restaurant, this cafe offers one of the best coffees in town, a great selection of desserts and one of the most cozy environments you can ever get in the city. Try their Mud Cake for sure.</string>
    <string name="land1_name">Mindrolling Monastery</string>
    <string name="land1_desc">Located in Clement Town, Mindrolling Monastry is a beautiful Buddhist monastry . The Stupa is open everyday of the week from 9:00 a.m. The great Stupa is 185 feet tall and 100 square feet in width. It is the world\'s largest Stupa and is a magnificent example of Buddhist art and architecture. The Stupa is surrounded by a 2-acre landscaped garden. On the facade of the Stupa, Maitreya, the future Buddha, has been beautifully painted. Descending the steps is the present Buddha, the Buddha Shakyamuni. On the several floors inside the Stupa are shrine rooms with elaborate murals executed in the finest tradition of Tibetan Buddhist art. Sacred relics have also been placed in the Stupa. Constructed to benefit all beings and dedicated to world peace, the Great Stupa was inaugurated on 28th of October, 2002.</string>
    <string name="land2_name">Clock Tower</string>
    <string name="land2_desc">The Clock Tower in Dehradun is the most renowned landmark of the city. The Clock Tower has six faces and it’s unique hexagonal architecture lending it heritage value. The Clock Tower is the most aesthetic structure in the city. The original name Of Clock Tower was Balbir Tower. It was built to commemorate India’s independence. The foundation stone was laid on July 2, 1948, by the Governor of UP, Sarojini Naidu. The Clock Tower was completed in 1953 and was inaugurated by Lal Bahadur Shastri.</string>
    <string name="land3_name">Forest Research Institute (FRI)</string>
    <string name="land3_desc">Located to the northwest of the city center, on the Kaulagarh Road, is the vast campus of the Forest Research Institute (FRI). Established by the British in 1906; the institute constantly strives towards the preservation of the various species of India\'s forest wealth and is one of the best institutes in the world on the science of forestry. The six museums located within its premise house diverse specimens of Indian flora and fauna and remain open for the public on weekdays. It is sheer pleasure to stroll in the verdant FRI campus.</string>
    <string name="land4_name">Survey Of India</string>
    <string name="land4_desc">Established in 1767, the office of Survey of India is located at a distance of 4 km from the city centre and forms an important landmark of the place. A repository of ancient maps and documents; it determined the height of Mount Everest, under the initiative of Sir George Everest; the then Surveyor of India. The peak was later named after him. It is a must-visit, especially if you are on the lookout for ancient maps.</string>
    <string name="land5_name">Chetwode Hall</string>
    <string name="land5_desc">It is a matter of pride that the great Indian Military Academy is located in Dehradun. India is the fifth largest nation in regards to the military power possessed. The Indian army possesses the latest and sophisticated ammunition which are displayed in Chetwode Hall. Apart from direct displays this museum also shows video clips describing various weapons. This war gallery serves as a prominent part of the Indian Military Academy (IMA).</string>
    <string name="land9_name">Wadia Institute Of Himalayan Geology</string>
    <string name="land9_desc">One of the best institutes of the country on Himalayan Geology, Wadia Institute conducts various studies and research works on the subject. It also houses a museum that displays the geological diversity of the Indian subcontinent, with its different samples of rocks and semi-precious stones. With the display of the fossils unearthed in the Himalayan region, the institute also throws light on the birth of the Himalayas.</string>
    <string name="land6_name">Sahastradhara</string>
    <string name="land6_desc">Located around 14 km from the city centre, the cold sulphur spring of Sahastradhara is believed to have healing powers. People visit the place to bathe in the therapeutic waters of the spring and the dripping caves nearby, to get rid of various skin diseases. Many people also bathe here for fun. With its picturesque surroundings and a 9-meter high waterfall, the place also serves as an ideal picnic spot.</string>
    <string name="land7_name">Malsi Deer Park</string>
    <string name="land7_desc">Situated at a distance of 10 km from Dehradun, en-route to Mussoorie, this park lies on the foothills of the Shivalik mountain range. With its tranquil atmosphere and its collection of deer, neelgai, ducks and rare birds, this sanctuary delights the children no end. People traveling to Mussoorie generally halt here for a short break, before resuming their journey. The mini-zoo, coupled with a children park with lots of swings, makes it very popular among children. Refreshments are available and one can have a picnic lunch here amongst the verdant surroundings but be careful because monkeys are always lurking around waiting to grab the food.</string>
    <string name="land8_name">Robbers Cave</string>
    <string name="land8_desc">Famous as \'Guchu Pani\' among the locals; the Robbers Cave located at a distance of 8 km from the city centre and 1 km from the nearby village of Anarwala. At this place, one can witness a strange phenomenon of nature - a stream of water gushes underground and quite mysteriously, re-appears a few meters away. The cave itself is a beautiful sight but sadly, rampant commercialization has marred the nearby surroundings so much so that one can hardly find a spot to spread out a picnic lunch.</string>
    <string name="pil1_name">Tapkeshwar Temple</string>
    <string name="pil1_desc">This ancient Shiva temple is situated on the banks of a rivulet, in the Garhi Cantt area of Dehradun. The temple is well connected by road. It is named Tapkeshwar as water droplets, originating from a rock, fall drop by drop on the Shivling placed in the shrine. Annually, a fair is held here on the occasion of Shivratri.</string>
    <string name="pil2_name">Laxman Siddh</string>
    <string name="pil2_desc">12 km away from Dehradun, on the Rishikesh route is a famous temple known as the Laxman Siddh. Legend has it that a sage called Swami Laxman Siddh underwent penance over here. Due to easy accessibility the temple is visited by a large number of devotees and tourists especially on Sundays.</string>
    <string name="pil3_name">Chandrabani</string>
    <string name="pil3_desc">Situated 7 km from Dehradun, on the Dehradun - Delhi road is the famous temple of Chandrabani (Gautam Kund). According to the mythological beliefs, this spot was inhabited by Maharishi Gautam, his wife and daughter Anjani. It is believed that the daugher of heaven, Ganga had manifested herself on this spot which is now popularly known as the Gautam Kund. Every year devotees, in large numbers, take a dip in the holy Kund. This place is a beautiful tourist spot located in the midst of Shivalik hills just 2 km away from the main road.</string>
    <string name="pil4_name">Santla Devi Temple</string>
    <string name="pil4_desc">15 km from Dehradun on a steep cliff of 2,083 m is located the temple of Santla Devi. To reach the temple of Santla Devi, one passes through Garhi Cantt and Punjabiwal villages. One can utilize the bus facilities till Jaitanwala, then it is a 2 km drive to Punjabiwala by a Jeep or any light vehicle and further it is a 2 km trek from Punjabiwala to the temple. Legend has it that Santla Devi along with her brother on realizing that they would not be able to face the Mughal army, abandoned their weapons and began to pray. A light flickered and within moments, they both were transformed into stone images. Saturday marks the transformation of the Goddess into stone. Since then special obeisance is paid on Saturdays. The temple stands as a symbol of the faith people have in the temple and has great cultural and religious significance.</string>
    <string name="pil6_name">Bhadraj Temple</string>
    <string name="pil6_desc">Situated on the extreme western region of Mussoorie town, this temple is dedicated to Lord Balbhadra, brother of Shri Krishna. About 15 km from Mussoorie, Bhadraj offers a commanding view of the Doon Valley and Chakrata ranges.</string>
    <string name="pil7_name">Surkhanda Devi</string>
    <string name="pil7_desc">Situated at an elevation of 3,030 meters above sea level near village Kaddukhal, the temple of Surkanda Devi is about 40 km from Mussoorie and 8 km from Dhanolti. Visitors can go up to Kaddukhal (Devasthali) by bus or by car from where the temple is about 2 km on foot.</string>
    <string name="pil8_name">Jwalaji Temple (Benog Hill)</string>
    <string name="pil8_desc">9 km to the west of Mussoorie and at an altitude of 2104 meters is the Jwalaji Temple. It is situated on the top of the Benog Hill and has an idol of Mata Durga in it. The temple is surrounded by these forests and offers a panoramic view of the Himalayan peaks and Doon valley.</string>
    <string name="pil9_name">Nag Devta Temple</string>
    <string name="pil9_desc">This ancient temple, situated on Cart Road is about 6 km from Mussoorie.</string>
    <string name="pil5_name">Parkasheshwar Temple</string>
    <string name="pil5_desc">20 km from Mussoorie on Dehradun road lies this temple dedicated to Lord Shiva. Unique for the fact that no offerings are accepted and very tasty Prasad is served.</string>
    <string name="sh1_name">Rajpur Road</string>
    <string name="sh1_desc">This is Dehradun’s most famous road. Long drives down Rajpur Road are a part of every Doonite’s memories. Rajpur Road starts from the Clock Tower and ends at the Rajpur village. The Astley Hall area on Rajpur Road is a favourite hang out spot. Astley Hall has fast food chains, a gaming parlour, ice cream parlours and a number of good restaurants and shops. Most of the top brands in the country have their retail outlets on Rajpur Road.</string>
    <string name="sh2_name">Paltan Bazaar</string>
    <string name="sh2_desc">The Paltan Bazaar is the main market of Dehradun. It is located right in the heart of the town, near the Clock Tower. It is a shopper’s paradise with all kinds of merchandise. One can buy Dehradun’s specialties - Basmati Rice and hand made woollens from here. The side pavements are heavily encroached and it is best covered on foot or a two wheeler. At the center of the Paltan Bazaar is the fruit and vegetable market. Rama Market in Paltan Bazaar is favorite haunt of ladies to purchase beautiful bed linen and export quality fabrics in pleasing prints. Many printer shops are also based here. For purchasing school and college books and stationery, ask for Dispensary Road in the Paltan Bazaar area. For those who believe in the power of herbs to cure all ailments, Dehradun has two well stocked stores famous for Jadi Bootis (herbs and medicinal plants) located near the Kotwali in Paltan Bazaar.</string>
    <string name="mall1_name">Crossroads Mall</string>
    <string name="mall1_desc">1, Old Survey Road, Dehradun, Uttarakhand.</string>
    <string name="mall2_name">City Junction Mall</string>
    <string name="mall2_desc">ISBT, Transport Nagar, Dehradun, Uttarakhand.</string>
    <string name="mall3_name">Parsvnath Eleganza Mall</string>
    <string name="mall3_desc">103, Rajpur Road, Near R.T.O. Office, Dehradun, Uttarakhand.</string>
    <string name="mall4_name">Times Square</string>
    <string name="mall4_desc">Near SBI Bank, Sahastradhara Road, Dehradun, Uttarakhand.</string>
    <string name="mall5_name">Vikas Cinemall</string>
    <string name="mall5_desc">Indira Nagar, Dehradun, Uttarakhand.</string>
    <string name="m1_name">PVR, Pacific Mall</string>
    <string name="m1_desc">+91 99135 25571</string>
    <string name="m2_name">Silver City Multiplex, Parsvnath Eleganza</string>
    <string name="m2_desc">+91 135 3298800</string>
    <string name="m3_name">BIG Cinemas, Vikas Cinemall</string>
    <string name="m3_desc">+91 135 3989404</string>
    <string name="m4_name">Glitz Cinemas, City Junction Mall</string>
    <string name="m4_desc">+91 135 2645986</string>
    <string name="m5_name">Orient, Rajpur Road</string>
    <string name="m5_desc">+91 135 2657260</string>
    <string name="m6_name">Prabhat, Chakrata Road</string>
    <string name="m6_desc">+91 135 2657274</string>
    <string name="m7_name">New Empire, Rajpur Road</string>
    <string name="m7_desc">+91 135 2652917</string>
    <string name="m8_name">Chayadeep, Rajpur Road</string>
    <string name="m8_desc">+91 135 2659009</string>
    <string name="m9_name">Payal, Rajpur Road</string>
    <string name="m9_desc">+91 135 2657077</string>
    <string name="m10_name">Natraj, Chakrata Road</string>
    <string name="m10_desc">+91 135 2657357</string>
    <string name="h1_name">Coronation Hospital</string>
    <string name="h1_desc">+91 135 2653984</string>
    <string name="h2_name">Doon Hospital</string>
    <string name="h2_desc">+91 135 2653523</string>
    <string name="h3_name">Doon Mahila Hospital</string>
    <string name="h3_desc">+91 135 2659236</string>
    <string name="h4_name">Himalyan Institute, Jolly Grant</string>
    <string name="h4_desc">+91 135 2412007</string>
    <string name="h5_name">CMI Hospital</string>
    <string name="h5_desc">+91 135 2720238</string>
    <string name="h6_name">Military Hospital (Cantt)</string>
    <string name="h6_desc">+91 135 2757288</string>
    <string name="h7_name">Mahant Indresh Hospital</string>
    <string name="h7_desc">+91 135 2522203</string>
    <string name="h8_name">ONGC Hospital Ltd</string>
    <string name="h8_desc">+91 135 2795554</string>
    <string name="h9_name">Aastha Hospital</string>
    <string name="h9_desc">+91 135 2764413</string>
    <string name="h10_name">Ashirwad Hospital</string>
    <string name="h10_desc">+91 135 2763600</string>
    <string name="h11_name">Param Hospital</string>
    <string name="h11_desc">+91 135 2673022</string>
    <string name="h12_name">Kalhan</string>
    <string name="h12_desc">+91 135 2742069</string>
    <string name="h13_name">Jyoti Nursing Home</string>
    <string name="h13_desc">+91 135 2657065</string>
    <string name="h14_name">Vaish Nursing Home</string>
    <string name="h14_desc">+91 135 2749267</string>
    <string name="h15_name">Apollo Clinic</string>
    <string name="h15_desc">+91 135 2628575</string>
    <string name="h16_name">Guru Tegh Bahadur Sahib Hospital</string>
    <string name="h16_desc">+91 135 2721615</string>
    <string name="e1_name">Police</string>
    <string name="e1_desc">100</string>
    <string name="e2_name">Fire Brigade</string>
    <string name="e2_desc">101</string>
    <string name="e3_name">Ambulance</string>
    <string name="e3_desc">102</string>
    <string name="e4_name">Emergency Services</string>
    <string name="e4_desc">108</string>
    <string name="e5_name">SSP</string>
    <string name="e5_desc">+91 135 2626020</string>
    <string name="e6_name">S.P. (City)</string>
    <string name="e6_desc">+91 135 2672201</string>
    <string name="e7_name">Fire Station (Gandhi Road)</string>
    <string name="e7_desc">+91 135 2657007</string>
    <string name="e8_name">Fire Station (Dilaram Baazar)</string>
    <string name="e8_desc">+91 135 2745857</string>
    <string name="e9_name">Fire Station (Ballupur Road)</string>
    <string name="e9_desc">+91 135 2782745</string>
    <string name="e10_name">Fire Station (Mussoorie)</string>
    <string name="e10_desc">+91 135 2632100</string>
    <string name="e11_name">Women Helpline</string>
    <string name="e11_desc">+91 135 2716239</string>
    <string name="b1_name">Ellora Bakers</string>
    <string name="b1_desc">+91 135 2657459</string>
    <string name="b2_name">Ellora\'s Melting Moments</string>
    <string name="b2_desc">+91 135 2714950</string>
    <string name="b3_name">Grand Bakers</string>
    <string name="b3_desc">+91 135 2654933</string>
    <string name="b4_name">Nany\'s Bakery</string>
    <string name="b4_desc">+91 135 2742000</string>
    <string name="b5_name">Opee\'s Bakers</string>
    <string name="b5_desc">+91 135 2740458</string>
    <string name="b6_name">Sunrise Bakers</string>
    <string name="b6_desc">+91 135 2653462</string>
    <string name="ff1_name">McDonald\'s</string>
    <string name="ff1_desc">The world famous burger chain has an outlet in the city\'s heart, Astley Hall.</string>
    <string name="ff2_name">Domino\'s Pizza</string>
    <string name="ff2_desc">Domino\'s Outlets are spread like topping all over the city. Locations are Rajpur Road, Saharanpur Road, Pacific Mall, Vikas Cinemall and Haridwar Road.</string>
    <string name="ff3_name">Pizza Hut</string>
    <string name="ff3_desc">Pizza Hut was the first fast-food chain the city ever received. You can find Pizza Hut outlets in Parsvnath Eleganza, Pacific Mall and Indira Nagar Colony.</string>
    <string name="ff4_name">KFC</string>
    <string name="ff4_desc">Finger-lickin\' good chicken available at Rajpur Road and Pacific Mall.</string>
    <string name="ff5_name">Subway</string>
    <string name="ff5_desc">If you\'re looking for some healthy choices, you can find Subway outlets in Pacific Mall and on Rajpur Road, near Clock Tower.</string>
    <string name="ff6_name">Dunkin Donuts</string>
    <string name="ff6_desc">In the mood for some donuts? Find Dunkin Donuts at Pacific Mall.</string>
    <string name="ff7_name">Burger King</string>
    <string name="ff7_desc">New in town, Burger King can be found in Pacific Mall, like everything else.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment"></string>
</resources>
